<div>
    <p>Dear <t t-out="object.partner_id.name" data-oe-t-inline="true" contenteditable="false"/>,</p>
    <p>
        Thank you for your interest in our services.
    </p>
    <p>
        The coordinates you are looking for are present in the database.
    </p>
    <br/>
    <p>
        There is <strong t-out="sum(object.order_line.mapped('product_uom_qty')) or 0" style="box-sizing:border-box;font-weight:500;" contenteditable="false"></strong> contacts in the selection.
    </p>
    <p>
       In the tailor-made selection formula, where we provide the contact list for you, you pay <strong t-out="object.order_line and object.order_line[0].price_unit or 0" style="box-sizing:border-box;font-weight:500;" contenteditable="false"></strong> EUR per contact. The contact list then costs <strong t-out="format_amount(object.amount_total, object.currency_id) or ''" style="box-sizing:border-box;font-weight:500;" contenteditable="false"></strong> incl. VAT.
    </p>

    <p>
        Attached you will find the quote. Please agree to sign this offer online via this link below.
    </p>
    <p>If this quote seems interesting to you, just sign it online via the link below.</p>
    <center>
        <a t-att-href="object.get_portal_url()" class="btn btn-primary" style="color: #fff;background-color: #007bff;border-color: #007bff;">LINK</a>
    </center>
    <br/>
    <p>
        You will then receive the Excel list with the requested contact details. You will receive the name of the organization,
         postal address, telephone number, surname, first name and title, position, e-mail address (direct),
         the language and gender of the contact person.
    </p>
    <p>
        Thus, upon receipt of your agreement, we will create the selection for you and deliver it to you.
    </p>
    <br/><br/>
    Don't hesitate to contact us if you have any questions.
    <br/>
    <t t-out="object.user_id.name" data-oe-t-inline="true" contenteditable="false"></t>
    <hr class="mt-8 mb-8"/>
    <div class="row">
        <div class="col-lg-8 col-md-8 col-sm-8 col-xs-12">
            <img t-att-src="'/logo.png?company=%s' % object.company_id.id" style="border-style: none; box-sizing: border-box; vertical-align: middle; padding: 0px; margin: 0px; height: 50px; width: 200px;" t-att-alt="'%s' % object.company_id.name" width="200px" height="100">
        </div>
        <div class="col-lg-4 col-md-4 col-sm-4 col-xs-12">
            <p style="margin:0px 0 12px 0;box-sizing:border-box;font-weight:bold;">Keizerslaan 34</p>
            <p style="margin:0px 0 12px 0;box-sizing:border-box;font-weight:bold;">1000 Brussel</p>
            <p style="margin:0px 0 12px 0;box-sizing:border-box;">+32 (0)2 213 85 00</p>
            <p style="margin:0px 0 12px 0;box-sizing:border-box;"><a target="_blank" href="https://www.pinakes.be/nl" style="text-decoration:none;box-sizing:border-box;background-color:transparent;color:blue;font-weight:bold">https://www.pinakes.be/nl</a></p>
        </div>
    </div>
    <div class="row">
        <div class="col-12">
            <small>Follow interesting news about appointments in our newsletter!</small>
            <small>
                The Pinakes database contains information such as contact details of political
                representatives, senior civil servants and decision-makers from Belgian,
                Luxembourg and European public administrations as well as from services and organizations in the welfare,
                health and of the non-market. Public administrations, institutions and legal entities governed by private
                law can thus inform data subjects of activities, products or services that may be of interest to them.
                We also process data for other purposes. We would like to point out that the processing of data is done
                in accordance with the legislation relating to the respect of privacy as well as the legislation relating
                to e-commerce in force. If you would like more information about how we process personal data,
                please see our <a target="_blank" href="https://www.pinakes.be/fr/vie-privee">Privacy Statement</a>. If you have any questions or remarks, do not hesitate to contact
                our DPO via <a href="mailto:dpo@pinakes.be">dpo@pinakes.be</a> or at the address; Boulevard de l'Empereur 34, 1000 Brussels.
            </small>
        </div>
    </div>
</div>
